Guide to the Polly Shackleton papers, 1894-1997 MS2031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject, chronological and correspondence files, 1970-1987; Series 10
  - Files C, 1970-1987; Series 10 Subseries 2
    - Chron File, 1986 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1979 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Chron File, 1981 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Chron File, 1982 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Chron File, 1980 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Chron File, 1977 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Chron File, 1984 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1983 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Chron File, 1978 July; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Chron File, 1976 July 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1975 July 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Chron File, 1975 July 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Chron File, 1976 July 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Chron File, 1985 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1986 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1979 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1981 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Chron File, 1982 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Chron File, 1980 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1976 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1977 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1984 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Chron File, 1983 June; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1975 June 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1978 June 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1977 June 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1975 June 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Chron File, 1978 June 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Chron File, 1975 June 03; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Chron File, 1986 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1975 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1979 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1981 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Chron File, 1982 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Chron File, 1980 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Chron File, 1984 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Chron File, 1985 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Chron File, 1983 March; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1978 March 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Chron File, 1976 March 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Chron File, 1977 March 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Chron File, 1978 March 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1976 March 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1977 March 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Chron File, 1985 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1986 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Chron File, 1978 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1979 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1981 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Chron File, 1982 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Chron File, 1980 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1984 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Chron File, 1983 May; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1975 May 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1976 May 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Chron File, 1977 May 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Chron File, 1975 May 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Chron File, 1976 May 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1977 May 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Chron File, 1975 May 03; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Chron File, 1975 May 04; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Chron File, 1985 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Chron File, 1974 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Chron File, 1975 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1978 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Chron File, 1981 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Chron File, 1979 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Chron File, 1980 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Chron File, 1984 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1983 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Chron File, 1976 November; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Chron File, 1977 November 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Chron File, 1977 November 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Chron File, 1985 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Chron File, 1978 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Chron File, 1979 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Chron File, 1980 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Chron File, 1984 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1983 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Chron File, 1975 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Chron File, 1976 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1981 October; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Chron File, 1975 October 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1977 October 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Chron File, 1977 October 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Chron File, 1985 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Chron File, 1976 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Chron File, 1978 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Chron File, 1979 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Chron File, 1981 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Chron File, 1980 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Chron File, 1977 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Chron File, 1984 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Chron File, 1983 September; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Chron File, 1975 September 01; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Chron File, 1975 September 02; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Associaiton Foxhall Village Citizens Association, 1975-1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Citizens Association American University Park Association, 1975-1978; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Association Burleith Citizens Association, 1984-1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Citizens Association Burleith Citizens Association, 1975-1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Association Burleith Citizens Association, 1958-1974; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Association Cathedral Heights - Cleveland Park Citizens Association, 1975-1978; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Association Chevy Chase Citizens Association, 1984-1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Association Chevy Chase Citizens Association, 1975-1980; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Citizens Association Chevy Chase Citizens Association, 1981-1983; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Association Citizens for City Living, 1970-1977; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Citizens Association Citizens Planning Coalition, 1979-1983; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Citizens Association Cleveland Park Citizens Association, 1976; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Citizens Association Coalition for Planned Environmental Development, 1978-1983; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Citizens Association Coalition for Planned Environmental Development, 1977-1978; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Citizens Association Committee of 100, 1975-1983; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Association D.C. Federation of Citizens Association, 1979-1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Association D.C. Federation of Citizens Association, 1974-1979; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Association Federation of Citizens Association of the District of Columbia, 1981-1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Association Forest Hills Citizens Association, 1975-1984; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Association Foxhall Community Association, 1976-1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Citizens Association Friendship Neighborhood Coalition, 1975-1985; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Citizens Association Frienship Citizens Association, 1977-1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Citizens Association Gateway Conominium Association, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Association Glover Park Citizens Association, 1977-1979; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Citizens Association MC Clean Gardens Residents Association, 1975-1979; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Citizens Association Neighboorhood Planning Council #2, 1975-1984; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Association Neighboorhood Planning Council #3, 1974; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Citizens Association Neighboorhood Planning Council #4, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Association Neighborhood Planning Council #6, 1976-1983; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Citizens Association North Cleveland Park Citizens Association, 1975-1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Citizens Association North Foxhall RD Citizens Association, 1977; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Citizens Association of Georgetown, 1979-1984; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Citizens Association of Georgetown, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Citizens Association of Georgetown, 1974-1976; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Citizens Association Palisades Citizens Association, 1975-1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Citizens Association Spring Valley Wesley Heights Citizens Association, 1976-1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Citizens Associatoin Burleith Citizens Associations, 1982-1984; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Committee Meeting, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Committee Meeting Georgetown Area Access, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA F/A Hearing on Water/Sewer Billing Procedures and Bill 4 - 340, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing on "Anti - Drunk Driving Act" Bill 4 - 389, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing Alley Closing 2, 1981-1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing Alley Closings, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing Bill 4 - 238 Abandoned Vehicle Removal Act, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing Bill 4 - 336, "Prohibit Free Cigarettes Distribution Act", 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing Bill 4 - 336, "Prohibit Free Cigarettes Distribution Act", 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing Disabled Parking Privilege Bills 4 - 45 and 4 - 298, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Hearing on Street/Alley Closing Procedures Act, Bill 40241, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting "Anti Drunk Driving Act" "Soil Conservation District", 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting "Disabled Parking Privileges Act" "Motor Vehicle Difiniation Act", 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Alley Closing, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Alley Closing (Ward 2), 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Alley Closing, RPP, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Bill 4 - 292, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Briefing by Dot on Registration, Foul ups and alley closings, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Bus Briefing Building Restriction Act, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Child Restraint, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Comments on Sidewalk Cafe and Abandoned Vehicle Removal, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Dot briefing on Bus Barns, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Drivers Ed, Kintner Alley CLosing Stable/Reliable Source, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Motor Vehicle Registration Amendments (Students), 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting Public Space Parking, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Meeting RPP, Alley Closing, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Public Hearing Alley Closing, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Public Hearing on Bill 4 - 337 Council Chairpersons, 1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Roundtable Bill 4 - 384 Solid Waste Disposal Fee, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Roundtable Bills 3 - 334, 3 - 335, 3 - 337, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Committee Meeting T/EA Roundtable Child Restraint Act, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Committee Meeting T/FA FY82 Budget Supplement Mark - Up Solid Waste Disposal Act, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Committee Meetings Alley Closing/Idaho/Maco, 1980; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Committee Meetings T/EA Hearing - Condo Trash Collection, 1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Committee Meetings T/EA Hearing - Motor Vehicle Registration, 1980-1981; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Complaint Logs, 1978-1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Complaint Logs, 1982-1983; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Complaint Logs, 1983-1985; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Condo - Conversion ANC, 1976-1978; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Condo Conversion 2512 Q Street, Undated; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Condo Conversion 2800 Wisconsin Ave., 1979; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Condo Conversion Legislation, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Condo Conversion Legislation, 1975-1979; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Condo Conversion Legislation, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Condo Conversion McLean Gardens, 1978; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Condo Conversion Miscellaneous, 1977-1979; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Condo Conversion Park Crest Tenants Organization, 1979; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Condo Conversion Statements and Correspondence, 1975; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Condo Conversion The Chesterfield, Undated; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Condo Conversion The Essex, 1977-1978; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Condo Conversion Ward Office Mail, Undated; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Congratulatory Correspondence, Acknowledgements and Clippings, 1970; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Response Cards (1 of 6), 1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Response Cards (2 of 6), 1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Response Cards (3 of 6), 1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Constituent Response Cards (4 of 6), 1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Constituent Response Cards (5 of 6), 1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Constituent Response Cards (6 of 6), 1986; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Consumer Affairs, 1968; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Consumer Affairs: Congressional Correspondence, 1968; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Contribution Thank Yous - to be written, 1978-1982; Series 10 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Files D-G, 1970-1987; Series 10 Subseries 3
    - DES Water Bills, 1975; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - DES/Water Bill, 1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - DES/Water Bill, 1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - DES/Water Bill, 1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - DES/Water Bill, 1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - DES/Water Bills, 1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - DES/Water Bills, 1981; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - DES/Water Bills, 1981; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - DES/Water Bills, 1981; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - DES/Water Bills, 1981; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - DES/Water Bills, 1981; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - DHCD Building and Zoning Regulations Regulations Administration, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - DHCD Building and Zoning Regulations Regulations Administration, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - DHCD Building and Zoning Regulations Regulations Administration, 1976-1979; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - DHCD Housing Regulation Division, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - DHCD Housing Regulation Division, 1983-1985; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - DHCD Miscellaneous, 1978-1981; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - DHCD Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - DHCD Rent Control, 1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - DHCD Rent Control, 1976; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - DHCD Rent Control, 1975; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - DHCD Student Financial Aid Program, 1975-1979; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - DHR Elderly, 1975-1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - DHR Food Stamp Program, 1978-1979; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - DHR Miscellaneous, 1975-1976; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - DHR Miscellaneous, 1976-1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - DHR Miscellaneous, 1977-1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - DHR Miscellaneous, 1975; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - DHR Miscellaneous, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - DHR Miscellaneous, 1978-1979; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - DOT - Traffic, 1982; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - DOT Auto Tag, 1973; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - DOT Auto Tag Fee, 1977-1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - DOT Bicycles, 1975-1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - DOT Construction and Maintenance, 1975-1976; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - DOT Construction and Maintenance, 1978-1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - DOT Construction and Maintenance, 1981-1983; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - DOT Construction and Maintenance, 1985-1986; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - DOT Construction and Maintenance, 1984; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - DOT CS - DOT Public Space, 1983-1986; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - DOT CS/DOT - Bicycles, 1983; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - DOT CS/DOT Miscellaneous, 1979-1983; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - DOT Hackers License Appeal Board, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - DOT Hackers License Appeal Board, 1975-1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - DOT Motor Vehicle Services, 1975-1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - DOT Motor Vehicle Services, 1977-1982; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - DOT Motor Vehicle Services, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - DOT Parking, 1979-1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - DOT Parking, 1979; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - DOT Parking, 1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - DOT Parking, 1982; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - DOT Parking, 1983-1985; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - DOT Parking - PEP/Adj., 1981-1984; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - DOT Street Lighting, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - DOT Street Lights, 1979-1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - DOT Street Sanding, 1977-1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - DOT Street Sanding, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - DOT Traffic, 1981-1982; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - DOT Traffic, 1985-1986; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - DOT Traffic, 1984-1985; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - DOT Traffic Misc., 1975; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - DOT Traffic Misc., 1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - DOT Traffic Misc., 1977; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - DOT Traffic Misc., 1976; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - DOT Traffic Misc., 1975; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - DOT Traffic Misc., 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - DOT Traffic Signals, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - DOT Traffic Signals, 1975-1976; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - DOT Traffic Signals, 1975; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - DOT Traffic Signs, 1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - DOT Traffic Signs, 1974-1976; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - DOT Traffic Signs, 1977-1978; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - DOT Traffic Signs, 1978-1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - DOT Trees and Landscaping, 1977-1980; Series 10 Sub series 3 (Box 98, Folder 6)